amnesiagame.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Frictional Games

We take your privacy and security seriously. In this Privacy Policy you will find information on how we access and process your information. You can always contact us with any questions, or if you want us to delete your data.

**Games**

All customer data saved on third-party softwares and sites. We do not track achievments, trophies and similar data, other than the publically available information.

In order to track game progress, the games read save data that the game has created. These save files include the game's state and the date it was stored. For certain services this data is saved on the service's servers, and we load that back in return to get hold of your save data.

**Contact form**

The contact form is a tool for site visitors to contact the company.

The contact requests are sent to an affiliated email address. The email service provider Googlemail [complies to GDPR rules](https://cloud.google.com/security/gdpr/). The emails are stored according to secure methods. The emails are sent according to secure methods, in this case the SSL protocol.

In addition to the email, the site saves the following information in MySQL database:  
\- Name (or pseudonym)  
\- Email address  
\- Sent message and title  
\- IP address

Contact form information is only used to deal with information provided in the contact form. The information or contact information is NOT used for any other purposes, such as marketing ur subscribing to a newsletter.

**Recruitment**

By sending us your application, you give us permission to store your personal information and attachments. We may contact you with opportunities at a later point in time.

The applications are stored for two years, after which they are deleted. We store all applications in a secure system. If you want your your information removed earlier, please contact us through our Contact form.

Please send all your applications to [apply@frictionalgames.com](mailto:apply@frictionalgames.com), so they can be stored and deleted appropriately. Emails to other addresses will be forwarded to the aforementioned email manually.  
Forum

The forum currently saves the following data on signed up users:

Required information:  
\- Email address: used for signup.  
\- Username: used for identification.  
\- Password: encrypted, stored on MySQL.  
\- IP address: used for identifying and blocking spam.

Public information:  
\- Registration date: user identification.  
\- Last active date: user status identification.  
\- Post count: user status verification.  
\- Reputation: user status verification.  
\- User group: user status identification.

Voluntary information:  
\- Date of birth  
\- Location  
\- Website  
\- Custom user title  
\- Signature  
\- Avatar  
\- Away status & reason  
\- Additional contact information

Information on required, public and voluntary information can be found on sign-up and elsewhere on the site.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone by websites you visit. They are widely used to make websites work, or for them to work more efficiently. They also provide information to the owners of the site.

Cookies generally contain two pieces of information: a site name, and a unique user ID. If you use the site again with the same device, the website will “know” you have visited before, and tailor your experience. Cookies help to improve the security of our websites and remember the settings you apply for your use of our websites.

You will be asked to consent to the storage of cookies on your device when you interact with one of our websites.

Frictional Games sites

\- PHPSESSID: IP address, date and time, and visited part of the site. Essential for crash report and spam management. Expiration: when a browser session ends.  
\- cookie-accepted: logs in the fact that you have consented to the use of cookies, so it will not display the cookie message again until you have cleared your cookies. Expiration: when cookies are cleared.  
\- has_js: logs in if the user has javascript enabled. Expiration: when a browser session ends.

MyBB cookies (Forum)

MyBB cookies are used to keep track of forum login sessions and logging the user out after inactivity. You can view all MyBB cookies on [MyBB Cookies page](https://docs.mybb.com/1.8/development/cookies/).

Not logged in:  
\- mybb[lastvisit]: the last time of visit in the UNIX timestamp format. Expiration: 1 year.  
\- mybb[lastactive]: the last time that a forum page has been loaded, in the UNIX timestamp format. Expiration: 1 year.  
\- sid: session ID. Expiration: when a browsing session ends.

Logged in:  
\- acploginattempts: the number of ACP login attempts a user has had. Expiration: 1 year.  
\- collapsed: keeps track of which categories and boxes have been collapsed (as opposed to being expanded by default). Expiration: 1 year.  
\- loginattempts: The number of login attempts a user has had. Expiration: 1 year.  
\- mybb[announcements]: read announcement IDs. Expiration: when cookies are cleared.

Turning cookies off

You can change how cookies are stored on your machine by clicking on the 'Tools' menu in your internet browser for your device. You can also learn more about cookies by visiting the third party website [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which includes additional information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser. For more information about these controls, visit your browser or device manuals. 

**Links to other websites**

This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.

**Data sharing**

Required by law: We may disclose your information to the extent that we are required to do so by law (which may include to government bodies and law enforcement agencies); in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; and in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention).

Enforcement: We may disclose your personal information to third parties in order to enforce or apply the terms of agreements, to investigate potential breaches or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our customers or others.

**Changes to this privacy notice**

We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated in May 2018.

**Contact us**

To request information about our privacy policy, please contact us through our Contact page. To make sure we read your message, please mention privacy policy in the title.

You can request your data to be deleted from our forum, recruitment system and emails. Please contact us through our [Contact page](https://www.frictionalgames.com/site/contact), and mention data deletion in the title.
